const kidsMathsQuestionsAndAnswers = [
   {
      "id":"1",
      "question":"What is the next prime number after 7?",
      "optionOne":"9",
      "optionTwo":"11",
      "optionThree":"13",
      "optionFour":"15",
      "correctAnswer":"11"
   },
   {
      "id":"2",
      "question":"The perimeter of a circle is also known as what?",
      "optionOne":"Area",
      "optionTwo":"Square",
      "optionThree":"Circumference",
      "optionFour":"None",
      "correctAnswer":"Circumference"
   },
   {
      "id":"3",
      "question":"65 – 43 = ?",
      "optionOne":"22",
      "optionTwo":"32",
      "optionThree":"23",
      "optionFour":"33",
      "correctAnswer":"22"
   },
   {
      "id":"4",
      "question":"True or false? A convex shape curves outwards.",
      "optionOne":"TRUE",
      "optionTwo":"FALSE",
      "optionThree":"NA",
      "optionFour":"None",
      "correctAnswer":"TRUE"
   },
   {
      "id":"5",
      "question":"What does the square root of 144 equal?",
      "optionOne":"10",
      "optionTwo":"11",
      "optionThree":"12",
      "optionFour":"13",
      "correctAnswer":"12"
   },
   {
      "id":"6",
      "question":"True or false? Pi can be correctly written as a fraction.",
      "optionOne":"TRUE",
      "optionTwo":"FALSE",
      "optionThree":"NA",
      "optionFour":"None",
      "correctAnswer":"FALSE"
   },
   {
      "id":"7",
      "question":"What comes after a million, billion and trillion?",
      "optionOne":"Zillion",
      "optionTwo":"Decillion",
      "optionThree":"Vigintillion",
      "optionFour":"Quadrillion",
      "correctAnswer":"Quadrillion"
   },
   {
      "id":"8",
      "question":"52 divided by 4 equals what?",
      "optionOne":"11",
      "optionTwo":"12",
      "optionThree":"13",
      "optionFour":"14",
      "correctAnswer":"13"
   },
   {
      "id":"9",
      "question":"What is the bigger number, a googol or a billion?",
      "optionOne":"Googol",
      "optionTwo":"Billion",
      "optionThree":"Equal",
      "optionFour":"None",
      "correctAnswer":"Googol"
   },
   {
      "id":"10",
      "question":"True or false? Opposite angles of a parallelogram are equal.",
      "optionOne":"TRUE",
      "optionTwo":"FALSE",
      "optionThree":"NA",
      "optionFour":"None",
      "correctAnswer":"TRUE"
   },
   {
      "id":"11",
      "question":"87 + 56 = ?",
      "optionOne":"133",
      "optionTwo":"134",
      "optionThree":"143",
      "optionFour":"144",
      "correctAnswer":"143"
   },
   {
      "id":"12",
      "question":"How many sides does a nonagon have?",
      "optionOne":"7",
      "optionTwo":"9",
      "optionThree":"11",
      "optionFour":"13",
      "correctAnswer":"9"
   },
   {
      "id":"13",
      "question":"True or false? -2 is an integer.",
      "optionOne":"TRUE",
      "optionTwo":"FALSE",
      "optionThree":"NA",
      "optionFour":"None",
      "correctAnswer":"TRUE"
   },
   {
      "id":"14",
      "question":"What is the next number in the Fibonacci sequence: 0, 1, 1, 2, 3, 5, 8, 13, 21, 34, ?",
      "optionOne":"52",
      "optionTwo":"53",
      "optionThree":"54",
      "optionFour":"55",
      "correctAnswer":"55"
   },
   {
      "id":"15",
      "question":"7 x 9 = ?",
      "optionOne":"43",
      "optionTwo":"53",
      "optionThree":"63",
      "optionFour":"73",
      "correctAnswer":"63"
   },
   {
      "id":"16",
      "question":"True or false? In an isosceles triangle all sides are unequal.",
      "optionOne":"TRUE",
      "optionTwo":"FALSE",
      "optionThree":"Depends",
      "optionFour":"None",
      "correctAnswer":"FALSE"
   },
   {
      "id":"17",
      "question":"In statistics, the middle value of an ordered set of values is called what?",
      "optionOne":"Approximate",
      "optionTwo":"Average",
      "optionThree":"Median",
      "optionFour":"None",
      "correctAnswer":"Median"
   },
   {
      "id":"18",
      "question":"What does 3 squared equal?",
      "optionOne":"3",
      "optionTwo":"6",
      "optionThree":"9",
      "optionFour":"12",
      "correctAnswer":"9"
   },
   {
      "id":"20",
      "question":"5 to the power of 0 equals what?",
      "optionOne":"1",
      "optionTwo":"5",
      "optionThree":"25",
      "optionFour":"125",
      "correctAnswer":"1"
   },
   {
      "id":"21",
      "question":"What 2D shape has 3 sides?",
      "optionOne":"Rectangle",
      "optionTwo":"Triangle",
      "optionThree":"Octagon",
      "optionFour":"Circle",
      "correctAnswer":"Triangle"
   },
   {
      "id":"22",
      "question":"How many square faces does a cube have?",
      "optionOne":"6",
      "optionTwo":"7",
      "optionThree":"8",
      "optionFour":"9",
      "correctAnswer":"6"
   },
   {
      "id":"23",
      "question":"What do you call a perfectly round 3D shape that looks like a ball? ",
      "optionOne":"Circle",
      "optionTwo":"Square",
      "optionThree":"Sphere",
      "optionFour":"Rectangle",
      "correctAnswer":"Sphere"
   },
   {
      "id":"24",
      "question":"How many sides does an octagon have? ",
      "optionOne":"6",
      "optionTwo":"7",
      "optionThree":"8",
      "optionFour":"9",
      "correctAnswer":"8"
   },
   {
      "id":"25",
      "question":"What 2D shape has 5 sides?",
      "optionOne":"Rectangle",
      "optionTwo":"Triangle",
      "optionThree":"Octagon",
      "optionFour":"Pentagon",
      "correctAnswer":"Pentagon"
   },
   {
      "id":"26",
      "question":"How many triangular faces does a square pyramid have?",
      "optionOne":"3",
      "optionTwo":"4",
      "optionThree":"5",
      "optionFour":"6",
      "correctAnswer":"4"
   },
   {
      "id":"27",
      "question":"What shape is the base of a cylinder?",
      "optionOne":"Circle",
      "optionTwo":"Sphere",
      "optionThree":"Square",
      "optionFour":"Pentagon",
      "correctAnswer":"Circle"
   },
   {
      "id":"28",
      "question":"How many sets of parallel sides does a parallelogram have?",
      "optionOne":"5",
      "optionTwo":"4",
      "optionThree":"3",
      "optionFour":"2",
      "correctAnswer":"2"
   },
   {
      "id":"29",
      "question":"What 2D shape has 6 sides? ",
      "optionOne":"Square",
      "optionTwo":"Pentagon",
      "optionThree":"Octagon",
      "optionFour":"Hexagon",
      "correctAnswer":"Hexagon"
   },
   {
      "id":"30",
      "question":"How many sides does a decagon have?",
      "optionOne":"8",
      "optionTwo":"9",
      "optionThree":"10",
      "optionFour":"11",
      "correctAnswer":"10"
   },
   {
      "id":"31",
      "question":"",
      "optionOne":"",
      "optionTwo":"",
      "optionThree":"",
      "optionFour":"",
      "correctAnswer":""
   }
];

export default kidsMathsQuestionsAndAnswers;